Guide to the Manbites Dog Theater Records, 1987-2017 and undated RL.11437
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Theater Seasons, 1987-2017 and undated; 1
  - 2005-2006 Season, 19
    - After the Deluge, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Back of the Throat, 2005 (Box 6)
    - piece-meal (sic), 2005 (Box 10)
      both hands theatre company (sic); marketing materials, newspaper clipping, box office reports
    - Tiny Ninja Theater presents Hamlet, 2005 (Box 10)
    - Speak Truth to Power, 2006 (Box 10)
      Contracts, receipts
    - The Last Two Minutes of the Complete Works of Henrik Ibsen, 2006; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - The Fall to Earth, 2006 (Box 10)
    - Three Sisters (on Ice), 2006 (Box 10)
    - One by One by Once Upon a Time, 2006 (Box 10)
    - Thom Pain (based on nothing), 2006 (Box 10)
    - brooms: a play about saying yes (sic), 2006 (Box 10)
      both hands theatre company (sic); marketing materials, box office reports
    - Movies at Manbites, 2006 (Box 10)
  - 2006-2007 Season, 20
    - Season brochure, 2006 (Box 10)
    - Season brochure, 2006 (Box 16)
    - My Name is Rachel Corrie, 2006 (Box 10)
    - The Cherry Orchard, 2006 (Box 10)
    - Exactly What T(w)o Do, 2006 (Box 16)
    - In the Doghouse, 2007; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - An Oak Tree, 2007; 5 folders (Box 10)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, correspondence, photographs
    - An Oak Tree photos, 2007 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0011)
      "Photos oak tree"
    - An Oak Tree CD 1, 2007 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0011)
    - An Oak Tree CD 2, 2007 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0012)
    - An Oak Tree Stage CD, 2007 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0013)
    - Beyond Belief, 2007; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Cornucopia of Me, 2007 (Box 10)
    - The Pillowman, 2007; 5 folders (Box 10)
      Reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, budgets
    - The Pillowman color photos, 2007 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0010)
      "Pillowman color photos by Alan Dehmer"
    - At the Vanishing Point, 2007; 6 folders (Box 10)
    - At the Vanishing Point, 2007 (Box 16)
    - At the Vanishing Point disc 1, 2007 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0005)
      "At the Vanishing Point Disc 1"
    - At the Vanishing Point disc 2, 2007 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0006)
      "At the Vanishing Point Disc 2"
    - At the Vanishing Point color photos, 2007 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0007)
      "At the Vanishing Point color photos by Alan Dehmer"
    - At the Vanishing Point powerpoint, 2007 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0008)
      "Meatyard PP"
    - At the Vanishing Point pre-show, 2007 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0009)
      "At the Vanishing Point pre-show"
    - MUSE Festival correspondence and notes, 2007 (Box 10)
    - boyElroy (sic), 2007 (Box 10)
      MUSE Festival; marketing materials, box office reports, script
    - boyElroy (sic) sampler, 2007 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0004)
      "boyELROY Pig Men Sampler"
    - Cornucopia of Me, 2007 (Box 10)
      MUSE Festival; marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports
    - Assembly!; Rehearsing A Public Ritual for the Founding of the Land of Apocryphy, 2007 (Box 10)
      MUSE Festival; marketing materials, newspaper clipping, box office reports
    - The Stonewater Rapture, 2007 (Box 10)
      MUSE Festival; marketing materials, box office reports
    - Live @ the Dog (sic), 2007 (Box 10)
    - Black Poetry, 2007 (Box 10)
      MUSE Festival; box office reports
    - Wine in the Wilderness, 2007 (Box 10)
    - Movies at Manbites, 2007 (Box 10)
  - 2007-2008 Season, 21
    - Season brochure, press materials and show rights, 2007 (Box 10)
    - Blue/Orange, 2007; 3 folders (Box 10)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, audition resumes
    - Blue/Orange DVD, 2007 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0016)
    - Blue Door, 2007 (Box 10)
      Proposal documents
    - Rabbit Hole, 2007 (Box 10)
    - Rabbit Hole DVD, 2007 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0014)
      "Rabbit Hole master"
    - Rabbit Hole DVD, 2007 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0015)
      "Rabbit Hole"
    - Hello Penis: A Man-ifesto, 2007 (Box 12)
    - My Lovely Suicides, 2007 (Box 12)
    - holding pattern (sic), 2007 (Box 12)
    - Found Magazine vs. PostSecret (sic), 2007 (Box 12)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, correspondence
    - Europe Central, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Europe Central DVD, 2008 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0026)
      "Europe Central, Little Green Pig Theatrical Concern, World Premiere"
    - Dying City, 2008 (Box 12)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, script
    - Beyond Belief, 2008 (Box 12)
      Reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, correspondence
    - Black Poetry, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Fistful of Love, 2008 (Box 12)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, budgets, receipts
    - Fistful of Love CD-R, 2008 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0012)
      "With fistful of love and gratitude"
    - The Non, 2008 (Box 12)
      Script, letter
    - Definition of a Hero, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Cornucopia of Me, 2008; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Goin' a Buffalo, 2008 (Box 12)
  - 2008-2009 Season, 22
    - Season brochure, press materials, and fundraising, 2008 (Box 12)
      Includes some correspondence
    - WUNC Pitches, 2008 (Box 12)
      Form letters
    - Black Bird, 2008 (Box 12)
      Correspondence
    - The Island, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Black Poetry, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Deer Hunting with Jesus, 2008 (Box 12)
      Marketing materials, newspaper, contracts, box office reports, scripts
    - The Secret Chord, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Act a Lady, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Hungry Ghost, 2009 (Box 12)
      Marketing materials, newspaper clippings, box office reports, correspondence
    - The Receptionist, 2009 (Box 12)
    - The Receptionist DVD, 2009 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0025)
      "The Receptionist"
    - The Receptionist (2009) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0047)
    - The Receptionist (2009) (2nd copy) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0048)
    - The Overwhelming, 2009 (Box 12)
      Marketing materials, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, scripts
    - Best of Flicker, 2009 (Box 12)
    - The Oldest Living Confederate Widow: Her Confession, 2009 (Box 12)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, photograph
    - Age of Arousal, 2009 (Box 12)
      Marketing materials, reviews, contracts, box office reports
    - Washing Machine, 2009 (Box 12)
    - Silver River (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0046)
  - 2009-2010 Season, 23
    - Season brochure, 2009 (Box 12)
    - Season intern applications and notes, 2009 (Box 12)
    - Age of Arousal, 2009 (Box 16)
    - Caleb Calypso and the Midnight Marauders, 2009 (Box 12)
    - The Italian Actress, 2009 (Box 13)
    - The Rule of Fate, 2009 (Box 13)
    - Jane Eyre, 2009 (Box 13)
    - Strange Beauty Film Festival, 2010 (Box 13)
    - Strange Beauty Film Festival DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0019)
      "Strange Beauty Festival Preview, 10 films"
    - Neighborhood 3: Requisition of Doom, 2010 (Box 13)
    - Neighborhood 3: Requisition of Doom DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0022)
      "Neighborhood 3"
    - Neighborhood 3: Requisition of Doom DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0023)
    - Neighborhood 3: Requisition of Doom DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0024)
      "Neighborhood 3 1st cut"; includes attached note
    - Now You See Me, 2010 (Box 13)
    - Now You See Me DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0004)
      "Now You See Me DVD-R"
    - Now You See Me DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0005)
    - The Oldest Living Confederate Widow: Her Confession, 2010 (Box 13)
    - The Oldest Living Confederate Widow: Her Confession DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0020)
      "Oldest Living Confederate Widow Tells All DVD-R"
    - The Oldest Living Confederate Widow: Her Confession DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0021)
    - God's Ear, 2010 (Box 13)
    - God's Ear DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0017)
      "God's Ear DVD-R"
    - God's Ear DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0018)
    - Blackbird, 2010 (Box 13)
  - 2010-2011 Season, 24
    - Season brochure, 2010 (Box 13)
    - Breadcrumbs, 2010 (Box 13)
    - Breadcrumbs, 2010 (Box 16)
    - Breadcrumbs DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0011)
      "Breadcrumbs"
    - Breadcrumbs DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0012)
      "Breadcrumbs DVD-R"
    - Breadcrumbs DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0013)
    - The Theme is Blackness, 2010 (Box 13)
    - Oh, the Humanity and other exclamations (sic), 2010 (Box 13)
      Marketing materials, reviews, contracts, box office reports, correspondence, script
    - Oh, the Humanity and other exclamations (sic) DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0009)
      "Oh the Humanity and other exclamations DVD-R"
    - Oh, the Humanity and other exclamations (sic) DVD, 2010 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0010)
      "Oh, the Humanity 1st cut"
    - Nightwork, 2011 (Box 13)
    - Nightwork DVD, 2011 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0006)
      "Nightwork 1st cut"
    - Nightwork DVD, 2011 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0007)
      "Nightwork DVD-R"
    - Nightwork DVD, 2011 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0008)
    - Strange Beauty Film Festival, 2011 (Box 13)
    - Now You See Me, 2011 (Box 13)
    - Archipelago, 2011 (Box 13)
    - Archipelago, 2011 (Box 16)
    - Jade City Chronicles, 2011 (Box 13)
    - Buddy Cop 2, 2011 (Box 13)
    - Buddy Cop 2 DVD, 2011 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0001)
      "Buddy Cop 2 DVD-R"
    - Buddy Cop 2 DVD, 2011 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0002)
    - Buddy Cop 2 DVD, 2011 (Box 7, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0003)
      "BC2 1st"
    - The Year of Empty Wine Bottles, 2011 (Box 13)
  - 2011-2012 Season
    - 11-12 Season brochures, 2011 (Box 18)
    - Middletown, 2011 (Box 18)
      Clipping, contracts, advertising, programs, and box office reports.
    - Middletown (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0027)
    - Middletown 2nd recording (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0028)
    - Edith, 2011 (Box 18)
      Edith Can Shoot Things and Hit Them. Program, contract, box office reports.
    - Edith Can Shoot Things and Hit Them (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0029)
    - Cape D, 2012 (Box 18)
      Cape Disappointment. Advertising, clipping, program, contract, box office reports.
    - Cape Disappointment (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0030)
    - In on It, 2012 (Box 18)
      Advertising, program, contract, theater review, notes on the play, box office reports.
    - One Little Word, 2012 (Box 18)
      Program, letter, advertising.
    - One Little Word sound cues (Box 21, Cd RL11437-OP-0013)
    - Living with the Tiger, 2011 (Box 18)
      Advertising, program, reviews, contract, mailings, press release, box office reports.
    - Hair, 2012 (Box 18)
      I Love my Hair When It's Good & Then Again When It Looks Defiant and Impressive. Program, advertising, clipping, box office reports, proposal, reviews.
    - Donald, 2012 (Box 18)
      Advertising, program, review, box office reports.
    - Strange Beauties, 2012 (Box 18)
      Advertising, contract, program, box office reports.
    - Strange Beauty film festival 2012 sampler (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0031)
    - Strange Beauty film festival 2012 still images (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0032)
    - 1*9*5*6, 2012 (Box 18)
      1*9*5*6 Degrees of Separation. Program, advertising, reviews, proposal, calendar, planning document, contract, box office reports.
  - 2012-2013 Season
    - Season brochure, 2012 (Box 16)
    - Brothers Size, 2012 (Box 18)
      Program, advertising, box office reports.
    - The Brothers Size master copy (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0033)
    - The Brothers Size (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0034)
    - The Brothers Size (2nd copy) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0035)
    - 70 Scenes, 2012 (Box 18)
      70 Scenes of Halloween. Program, advertising, reviews, card deck.
    - 70 Scenes of Halloween 1st cut (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0036)
    - 70 Scenes of Halloween (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0037)
    - New Electric, 2013 (Box 18)
      New Electric Ballroom. Budget, advertising, program, box office reports.
    - The New Electric Ballroom (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0038)
    - The New Electric Ballroom (2nd copy) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0039)
    - The Homosexuals, 2013; 2 folders (Box 18)
      Advertising, program, box office reports
    - The Homosexuals (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0040)
    - The Homosexuals (2nd copy) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0041)
    - 25th Birthday, 2012 (Box 18)
      Advertising
    - Book: Unleashed, undated (Box 18)
      Advertising, order form
    - Paper Hat, 2012 (Box 18)
      The Paper Hat Game. Program, advertising, reviews, box office reports
    - Election Central, 2012 (Box 18)
      Advertising, box office reports.
    - Strange Beauty, 2013 (Box 18)
      Program, reviews, box office reports.
    - Mike Daisey, 2013 (Box 18)
    - Lee and Lee, 2013 (Box 18)
    - LGP Clown Papers, 2013 (Box 18)
      der Klöwn schpanken effekt. Program, revews, box office reports
    - 12-13 season, 2012-2013 (Box 18)
    - Clippings, 1998-2006 (Box 18)
      Reviews
  - 2013-2014 Season
    - Clippings and pamphlets, 2013 (Box 18)
      Reviews, season brochures
    - Cock, 2013 (Box 18)
      Advertising, program, reviews, box office reports
    - Cock (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0052)
    - Cock (2nd copy) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0053)
    - Best of Enemies, 2013 (Box 18)
      Advertising, program, reviews
    - Best of Enemies box office, 2013; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Best of Enemies (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0042)
    - Best of Enemies (2nd copy) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0043)
    - Grounded, 2014 (Box 19)
      License agreement, reviews, box office reports
    - Grounded (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0044)
    - Spirits to Enforce, 2014; 2 folders (Box 19)
      Concept, advertising, program, box office reports, script
    - Spirits to Enforce photos (Box 21, Cd RL11437-OP-0014)
    - Spirits to Enforce (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0045)
    - Spirits to Enforce (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0054)
    - Spirits to Enforce (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0055)
    - Measure Back, 2013 (Box 19)
      Advertising, program, box office reports.
    - I Love My Hair, 2014; 2 folders (Box 19)
      I Love my Hair When It's Good & Then Again When It Looks Defiant and Impressive. Advertising, program, box office reports.
    - Republic, 2014 (Box 19)
    - Tarantino's Yellow Speedo box office, 2014 (Box 19)
      Program, box office reports.
    - Strange Beauty 2014 (Box 19)
  - 2014-2015 Season
    - Volunteer lists, 2014 (Box 19)
    - Best of Enemies sponsors, 2014 (Box 19)
      Letters, sponsor list
    - Best of Enemies box office reports, 2014; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Best of Enemies (2014 season) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0049)
    - Best of Enemies replacement DVD (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0050)
    - Best of Enemies (excerpt) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0051)
    - If My Feet, 2014 (Box 19)
      If My Feet Have Lost the Ground. Advertising, program, box office reports
    - I and You, 2014 (Box 19)
      Advertising, licensing, program, box office reports
    - I and You (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0056)
    - Habitus, 2015 (Box 19)
      Advertising, box office reports
    - Paris '76, 2015 (Box 19)
    - Fairytale Lives, 2015 (Box 19)
      Fairytale Lives of Russian Girls. Advertising, program, box office reports
    - Ass Saw Angel, 2015 (Box 19)
      And the Ass Saw the Angel. Program, box office reports
    - Coltrane rights, 2015 (Box 19)
      Licensing
  - 2015-2016 Season
    - 2015-2016 season (Box 19)
      Correspondence, notes, calendar, season pamphlets
    - Mr. Burns, 2015; 2 folders (Box 19)
      Play arrangements, calendar, box office reports, reviews
    - Tramp, 2015 (Box 19)
      The Tramp's New World. Advertising, program, reviews, box office reports
    - Brownsville, 2016 (Box 19)
      Brownsville Song (b-side for tray). Advertising, program, notes, box office reports
    - Brownsville Song (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0057)
    - The Nether, 2016 (Box 20)
      Play agreement, advertising, program, box office reports
    - The Nether (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0058)
    - Love and Info, 2016 (Box 20)
      Love and Information. Program, box office reports
    - The New Colossus, 2016 (Box 20)
  - 2016-2017 Season
    - 2016-2017 season pamphlets (Box 20)
    - Disney attendance reports, 2016 (Box 20)
      The Death of Walt Disney. Box office reports, advertising, program
    - Disney box office reports, 2016 (Box 20)
      The Death of Walt Disney.
    - Disney (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0059)
    - Disney (2nd copy) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0060)
    - The Trump Card, 2016 (Box 20)
      Advertising, program, script, box office reports
    - The Trump Card 2016 (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0061)
    - The Trump Card 2016 (2nd copy) (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0062)
    - Childress in Mind, 2017 (Box 20)
    - The Open House, 2017 (Box 20)
    - The Open House dvd (Box 21, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0063)
    - BlackOps Typog, 2017 (Box 20)
      The Typographer's Dream. Licensing, advertising, program, box office reports
    - Typographer (Box 22, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0064)
    - Orlando, 2017 (Box 20)
    - Bright Half Life, 2017 (Box 20)
    - Bright Half Life 2017 (Box 22, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0065)
    - Bright Half Life 2017 (2nd copy) (Box 22, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0066)
    - Miraculous, 2017 (Box 20)
      The Miraculous and the Mundane. Advertising, program, box office reports
    - Marjorie Prime, 2017 (Box 20)
    - Marjorie Prime 2017 (Box 22, Dvd RL11437-DVD-0067)
    - Hush Hush, 2017 (Box 20)
    - Transactors, 2017 (Box 20)
      Program, box office reports
    - Endless shrimp, 2017 (Box 20)
- Administrative Files, 1993-2009 and undated; 2
  Administrative Files comprises materials more broadly related to Manbites Dog operations. Includes some correspondence, marketing materials for acting classes, newspaper clippings, receipts and other financial records, and some fundraising materials, including grant applications. Also contains materials related to the National Endowment for the Arts, such as application materials, correspondence, and status reports. Includes a few videocassettes. Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Acting class, 1994 (Box 3)
    Marketing materials, newspaper clippings
  - Acting class, 2008 (Box 14)
    Roster, registration forms
  - Adopt-a-Photo, 2006 (Box 14)
    Correspondence, notes
  - Assorted newspaper clippings, 1993-1998; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Assorted ticket ledgers, 1988-1989 (Box 14)
    Ticket sales reports
  - Babcock Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Beer, wine, and concessions sales reports, 2003-2004 (Box 14)
  - Biddle Foundation/Past years, 1989-1992 (Box 15)
  - Blank form masters, 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Bryan Family Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Building fund receipts and statements, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - Credit card ticket sales reports, 2003-2009; 7 folders (Box 13)
    Tix.com weekly reports
  - Dog stuff, 1991 and undated (Box 15)
  - Donor cards and financial contributions, 2003-2009; 10 folders (Box 14)
  - Dramatists Guild grant, 2003 (Box 14)
    Correspondence, application materials
  - FEDAPT, 1989-1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Fundraising flyers and promotional materials, 2000-2006; 6 folders (Box 14)
  - Grants/Corporate, 1986 and undated (Box 15)
  - Grants/Durham Arts Council, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Grants/Durham Arts Council, 1990-1992 (Box 15)
  - Grants/Miscellaneous parts, undated (Box 15)
  - Grants/North Carolina Arts Council, 1989-1991 and undated; 5 folders (Box 15)
  - Great Human Race, 2003-2009; 3 folders (Box 14)
    Correspondence, flyers, memos, donation cards
  - Guide to Death and Dying? VHS, 1991 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0013)
  - Income Statements, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Letter from Joseph Papp/Public Theater, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Letters of Agreements, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Light filters, undated; 4 envelopes (Box 17)
  - Manbites Dog Inventory, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Manbites Dog Inventory VHS, 1992 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0009)
  - Manbites Dog Last Photo Shoot Party VHS, undated (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0004)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous press flyers, 1998-2003; 3 folders (Box 14)
    Manbites Dog flyers, On the Purple Circuit newsletters, assorted LGBTQ flyers and pamphlets
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1994-1998; 6 folders (Box 3)
    Correspondence, memos, application materials, status reports, financial documents
  - National Endowment for the Arts Grants, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - North Carolina Arts Council general support meeting, 2008 (Box 14)
    Memos, strategic plan
  - Payroll reports, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Petty cash forms, 1991; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Petty cash forms, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 15)
  - Publicity, 1988-1989 and undated (Box 15)
  - Receipts, 1998-2001; 39 folders (Box 8)
    Monthly receipts from production costs, payroll, and theater management
  - Receipts, 2001-2005; 44 folders (Box 9)
  - Receipts, 2005-2008; 42 folders (Box 11)
  - Receipts, 2009; 6 folders (Box 14)
  - Theater reviews, 1998-2001 (Box 15)
  - Untitled U-Matic, undated (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-UM-0001)
  - Untitled VHS, undated (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0012)
  - Used ticket vouchers, 2005-2006 (Box 14)
  - Z. Smith Reynolds Foundation, 1988-1992; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 7 Blowjobs strategy, 1992 (Box 15)